[
    {
      "num": "1",
      "question": "거두",
      "answer": "절미",
      "options": ["절미", "상련", "가상", "위복"]
    },
    {
      "num": "2",
      "question": "가담",
      "answer": "항설",
      "options": ["항설", "다감", "상련", "귀정"]
    },
    {
      "num": "3",
      "question": "가가",
      "answer": "호호",
      "options": ["전심", "소이", "호호", "동성"]
    },
    {
      "num": "4",
      "question": "감언",
      "answer": "이설",
      "options": ["하청", "자기", "이설", "위복"]
    },
    {
      "num": "5",
      "question": "경국",
      "answer": "지색",
      "options": ["초사", "지색", "소이", "항설"]
    },
    {
      "num": "6",
      "question": "고진",
      "answer": "감래",
      "options": ["가상", "호호", "이몽", "감래"]
    },
    {
      "num": "7",
      "question": "군계",
      "answer": "일학",
      "options": ["부동", "일악", "상련", "일학"]
    },
    {
      "num": "8",
      "question": "근묵",
      "answer": "자흑",
      "options": ["자흑", "위복", "묵근", "절미"]
    },
    {
      "num": "9",
      "question": "내유",
      "answer": "외강",
      "options": ["안석", "전심", "지색", "외강"]
    },
    {
      "num": "10",
      "question": "노심",
      "answer": "초사",
      "options": ["이설", "초사", "일학", "춘몽"]
    },
    {
      "num": "11",
      "question": "다정",
      "answer": "다감",
      "options": ["친절", "직입", "다감", "이몽"]
    },
    {
      "num": "12",
      "question": "단도",
      "answer": "직입",
      "options": ["항설", "자흑", "이몽", "직입"]
    },
    {
      "num": "13",
      "question": "대기",
      "answer": "만성",
      "options": ["외강", "만서", "만성", "가상"]
    },
    {
      "num": "14",
      "question": "대동",
      "answer": "소이",
      "options": ["사의", "소이", "대립", "동성"]
    },
    {
      "num": "15",
      "question": "동상",
      "answer": "이몽",
      "options": ["이몽", "지색", "위복", "감래"]
    },
    {
      "num": "16",
      "question": "동변",
      "answer": "상련",
      "options": ["상련", "호호", "이몽", "감래"]
    },
    {
      "num": "17",
      "question": "불가",
      "answer": "사의",
      "options": ["사리", "귀정", "사의", "감래"]
    },
    {
      "num": "18",
      "question": "백년",
      "answer": "하청",
      "options": ["하청", "천년", "손님", "소이"]
    },
    {
      "num": "19",
      "question": "사필",
      "answer": "귀정",
      "options": ["귀정", "감래", "사족", "춘몽"]
    },
    {
      "num": "20",
      "question": "설상",
      "answer": "가상",
      "options": ["감래", "가상", "하청", "부동"]
    },
    {
      "num": "21",
      "question": "속수",
      "answer": "무책",
      "options": ["무책", "자기", "살인", "이몽"]
    },
    {
      "num": "22",
      "question": "이심",
      "answer": "전심",
      "options": ["전심", "다감", "안석", "진심"]
    },
    {
      "num": "23",
      "question": "전화",
      "answer": "위복",
      "options": ["문자", "위복", "만성", "진화"]
    },
    {
      "num": "24",
      "question": "좌불",
      "answer": "안석",
      "options": ["안석", "전심", "인석", "부동"]
    },
    {
      "num": "25",
      "question": "일망",
      "answer": "타진",
      "options": ["타잔", "타진", "이망", "가상"]
    },
    {
      "num": "26",
      "question": "일장",
      "answer": "춘몽",
      "options": ["일몽", "하청", "감래", "춘몽"]
    },
    {
      "num": "27",
      "question": "자포",
      "answer": "자기",
      "options": ["감래", "자기", "반포", "일학"]
    },
    {
      "num": "28",
      "question": "촌철",
      "answer": "살인",
      "options": ["살인", "춘철", "소이", "다감"]
    },
    {
      "num": "29",
      "question": "이구",
      "answer": "동성",
      "options": ["아나", "삼구", "동성", "이성"]
    },
    {
      "num": "30",
      "question": "표리",
      "answer": "부동",
      "options": ["지계", "부동", "직입", "살인"]
    }
  ]
  